CODY LAWSON UI/UX ENGINEER

CONTACT

Email

cody@codylawsonux.com

Website

codylawsonux.com

SOCIAL

dribbble.com/_cody

instagram.com/codylawson

twitter.com/_codylawson

SKILLS

Prototyping

CSS

Javascript

Design

Data Visualization

HELLO!

My name is Cody Lawson, I'm a User Interface Engineer with over five years of experience. I did a short internship with Esri in 2012 and fulltime in 2013 developing GIS web applications for companies like Walmart, Guy Carpenter, PG&E, and government agencies like the National Geospatial Agency and the Department of Energy.

EXPERIENCE

2013-Present Esri

User Experience Engineer

At Esri I worked closely with our customers to translate their complicated business practices into easy to use, workflow driven, web applications. I Designed applications from the requirements gathering stage, through wireframe and prototyping, and eventually implemented my designs

on the front-end.

2012 Summer Esri

Internship: User Experience Engineer

Designed and implemented internal websites for Esri as well as design the UX and look and feel of Community

Maps, an Esri product released in 2013.

2010-2013 We3

Freelance Web Developer

Founded in partnership with two other students, we designed and implemented websites for a yoga studio, a marketing agency in Redlands, and developed a brand

guideline for a law office in San Diego.

EDUCATION

2009-2013

B.A. Web Design and Interactive Media

Art Institute of California

REFERENCES

Available upon request